MOHAMMAD SHAHIN A. ABDUL ZAMAD SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

RESUME OBJECTIVE

Web Developer with 5+ years of experience in designing and developing business logics, user interfaces, testing, debugging, and administrating database systems and servers. Proven ability in optimizing web functionalities that improve data retrieval and workflow efficiencies.

EXPERIENCE

September 2021 – May 2023 | Kuban Empire, Sydney, Australia **Web Developer**

- Revamped existing Laravel/VueJS system and converted into Laravel/ReactJS/Redux/NextJS project
- Perform third party API integrations
- Fixed bugs from existing websites and implemented enhancements that significantly improved web functionality and speed
- Optimized slow gueries

January 2021 - July 2021 | Pixzel Digital, Iligan City, Philippines

Team Lead / Senior Web Developer

- Spearheaded a team of 5 during the development of an ERP (Enterprise resource planning) Project for a construction company
- Successfully deployed an Online School Registration Portal for a client based in Singapore

October 2018 – December 2020 | Pixzel Digital, Iligan City, Philippines **Junior Web Developer**

- Developed an Order and Inventory Management System for a Medicine Supplier in Iligan City
- Developed and deployed an Accounting System to a School
- Developed a Warehouse Management System with eCommerce for a Hardware Company

+639 36 187 7324

mshahinaz29@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/shahin-az

lligan City, Philippines 9200

EDUCATION

2018

Mindanao State University

- Iligan Institute of

Technology

Iligan, Philippines

B.S. Information

Technology (major in

database systems)

*Cum Laude

SKILLS

PHP / Laravel

ReactJS/ VueJS / jQuery

JavaScript / TypeScript

Bootstrap / Tailwind / CSS

HTML5 / Ajax

MySQL / PostgreSQL

GIT

Github / Bitbucket

REST API